<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature id="info.julang.ide.feature" label="Julian Development Environment" version="0.1.31" provider-name="Ming Zhou"><!-- VERSION_ATTRIBUTE -->

   <description url="http://julang.info">
      This feature brings Julian development experience into Eclipse. It also integrates with (but doesn&apos;t require) JDT to allow a developer to write both Java and Julian in the same Java project.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://julang.info">
      MIT License
Copyright (c) 2020 Ming Zhou
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining
a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the
&quot;Software&quot;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including
without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish,
distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and
to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so,
subject to the following conditions:
The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES
OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.
IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE
FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION
OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION
WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
   </copyright>

   <url>
      <discovery label="Official Website" url="http://julang.info"/>
   </url>

   <includes
         id="org.eclipse.jdt"
         version="0.0.0"
         name="org.eclipse.jdt"
         optional="true"
         search-location="self"/>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.console"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.expressions"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.e4.core.services"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.e4.ui.css.swt.theme"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="info.julang.ide"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
